holidayiq.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy - HolidayIQ.com

##  Privacy Policy

This Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information collected by HolidayIQ ("HIQ"), a division of Leisure and Lifestyle Information Services Private Limited (the "Company"), when you access the website of HIQ or the Company. This policy does not apply to any entity not owned or controlled by the Company. This Policy may not be applicable to any information provided by you or on your behalf to HIQ or the Company in any other context. By accessing the HIQ website or any website of the Company, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy.

Collection of identifiable information

We will collect information from you if you choose to register for certain services provided by HIQ or the Company. The following specific information will be sought by us when requesting information about you: Name, Age/Date of Birth, Gender, Marital Status, Anniversary, Occupation, E-mail address, Holiday Preferences. 

HIQ uses the personal information collected from you for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain information, products and services; and to contact you about the latest about HolidayIQ and to complete your online profile on HolidayIQ.com. If you choose to connect your HolidayIQ account with Facebook, we will receive and retain basic account registration data you provide to Facebook, such as name, email address and location. We will not post anything to Facebook without your permission. 

Collection of non-identifiable information

This website may also provide us with certain non-personally identifiable information about your access to the website. Such information includes the IP address through which this site is accessed, the time at which this site is accessed and the specific portions of the website accessed by you. This information is not personally identifiable. 

HIQ uses this information as a feedback for improvement of the website, and for an analysis of the most frequently accessed portions of the website. This information will not at any stage be passed on to any person. 

Usage of cookies

The website uses cookies to improve your interactive sessions and to save time during access. When you return to the website, the information previously provided by you may be retrieved by your computer to enable certain features of the site without having to re-sign in, and allow you easier access to parts of the website customised by you. The cookie would allow your user name to be pre-entered so that only your password would need to be reentered by you at the time of sign in. The cookie would be stored on the hard disk of your computer and would not be available for access by us. 

The acceptance of cookies is dependent on the browser settings on the web-browser used by you. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone, nor will we use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. 

We will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information.
  * We need to share the information with business partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve any issue.
  * We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer.
  * If required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to / reply to any court orders / legal process / summons served on HIQ or on Leisure and Lifestyle Information Services Private Limited

Usage by our partners

We may from time to time engage external agencies to provide certain services on our behalf. These services may range from sending dispatches by mail, co-ordination of feedback, delivery of prizes (if any) etc. These external agencies are obligated to us in terms of confidentiality agreements and will be provided the personal information strictly on a need to know basis. 

Collection of information by third parties

We may disclose to third party services certain personally identifiable information listed below:

  * information you provide us such as name, email, mobile phone number
  * information we collect as you access and use our service, including device information, location and network carrier

This information is shared with third party service providers so that we can:

  * personalize the app for you 
  * perform behavioral analytics 

HIQ and Leisure and Lifestyle Information Services Private Limited may offer promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information and we encourage you to consult their privacy policies for more information on their privacy practices. 

Amendment of this policy

HIQ and/or the Company may from time to time amend this policy. When this policy is so amended, the last date of such amendment shall be indicated on this policy under the legend "Revised on 10 August 2014". In the event the amendment of this policy results in an enlargement of the scope of permitted disclosures of personally identifiable information, we shall obtain your consent before such disclosure. 

If you have questions about our privacy statement or our use of your information, or if you need help changing the information provided to us, please contact us by [clicking here](http://www.holidayiq.com/contactus.php)

This page is published and shall be construed in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3(11) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011 (?IT Rules?) that requires publishing the name of the Grievance Officer and his/her contact details on the website, such that users or any victim who suffers as a result of a violation of Rule 3 (outlined in our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use) by any other person, can notify their complaints to us. 

Further, as per Rule 3(4) of the IT Rules, the Grievance Officer shall acknowledge or respond to Your communication of violation of Rule 3, by any other person, within 36 (thirty six) hours, and the complaints shall be redressed within 1 (one) month from the date of receipt of the complaint. 

In accordance with Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under, the name and the contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below: 

Ms. Anusha Jha   
Address: # 3796, 7th Main, HAL II Stage, Bangalore - 560008   
Phone Number:080-40851222   
Email ID: grievance.officer@holidayiq.com 

If you do not wish to receive any further information about us, our products and our services, [please click here to unsubscribe.](http://www.holidayiq.com/unsubscribe.php)
